<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- titles -->
    <string-array name="str_array_external_libraries">
        <item>Butter Knife</item>
        <item>CircleImageView</item>
        <item>FastAdapter</item>
        <item>Jsoup</item>
        <item>MaterialDrawer</item>
        <item>RichEditor (Android)</item>
        <item>SQLCipher</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- author -->
    <string-array name="str_array_external_libraries_authors">
        <item>Jake Wharton</item>
        <item>Henning Dodenhof</item>
        <item>Mike Penz</item>
        <item>Jonathan Hedley</item>
        <item>Mike Penz</item>
        <item>Daichi Furiya</item>
        <item>Zetetic, LLC</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- descriptions -->
    <string-array name="str_array_external_libraries_descriptions">
        <item>@string/str_lib_butter_knife</item>
        <item>@string/str_lib_circle_imageview</item>
        <item>@string/str_lib_fast_adapter</item>
        <item>@string/str_lib_jsoup</item>
        <item>@string/str_lib_material_drawer</item>
        <item>@string/str_lib_rich_editor_android</item>
        <item>@string/str_lib_sqlcipher</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- urls -->
    <string-array name="str_array_external_libraries_urls">
        <item>https://github.com/JakeWharton/butterknife</item>
        <item>https://github.com/hdodenhof/CircleImageView</item>
        <item>https://github.com/mikepenz/FastAdapter</item>
        <item>https://github.com/jhy/jsoup</item>
        <item>https://github.com/mikepenz/MaterialDrawer</item>
        <item>https://github.com/wasabeef/richeditor-android</item>
        <item>https://www.zetetic.net/sqlcipher</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- lib descriptions -->
    <string name="str_lib_butter_knife">Field and method binding for Android views which uses
            annotation processing to generate boilerplate code for you.</string>
    <string name="str_lib_circle_imageview">A fast circular ImageView perfect for profile images.</string>
    <string name="str_lib_fast_adapter">The RecyclerView is one of the most used widgets in the Android world,
            and with it you have to implement an Adapter which provides the items
            for the view. Most use cases require the same base logic, but require
            you to write everything again and again. The FastAdapter is here
            to simplify this process. You don\'t have to worry about the adapter
            anymore. Just write the logic for how your view/item should look like,
            and you are done. This library has a fast and highly optimized core
            which provides core functionality, most apps require.</string>
    <string name="str_lib_jsoup">
            jsoup is a Java library for working with real-world HTML. It provides a very convenient API for
            extracting and manipulating data, using the best of DOM, CSS, and jquery-like methods.</string>
    <string name="str_lib_material_drawer">The MaterialDrawer library provides you with the easiest possible
            implementation of a navigation drawer for your application. Just Provide custom DrawerItems, custom colors,
            custom themes, etc. No limits for customizations.</string>
    <string name="str_lib_rich_editor_android">
        RichEditor for Android is a beautiful Rich Text WYSIWYG Editor for Android</string>
    <string name="str_lib_sqlcipher">
            SQLCipher extends the SQLite database library to add security enhancements
            that make it more suitable for encrypted local data storage such as on-the-fly encryption, tamper evidence,
            and key derivation. Based on SQLite, SQLCipher closely tracks SQLite and
            periodically integrates stable SQLite release features.

            SQLCipher is maintained by Zetetic, LLC, the official site can be found below</string>

</resources>